♪No one left to lean on♪
♪No way out, no place to run♪
♪Tears held back inside my eyes♪
♪I run against the wind and time♪
♪Loved and lost, regrets remain♪
♪But tears fall down like gentle rain♪
♪I look up strong, I grow with pride♪
♪Living life with heart untied♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪Break through the noise,
let them hear me♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪Break through the noise,
let them hear me♪
=Dragon King's Decree=
=Episode 9=
(Amity Hall)
(Plaque of Feng Qingfeng, head
of Feng Manor. Plaque of Feng Yunqiao.)
Miss Zhilou,
Mr. Feng and Miss Yunqiao have passed.
You are the Mr. Feng's last bloodline.
(Plaque of Qingfeng and Yunqiao)
We hope you'll become the head
and continue to protect Feng Manor.
I have never thought
this would happen.
Zhilou,
it's time
for you to learn about the family.
Is she...
my mother?
About your birth,
Mr. Feng's last wish,
and the future of Feng Manor.
You should decide
if you want to bear the responsibility
of these truths.
(Zhilou,)
(my dear daughter.)
(Yue, Feng Zhilou's Mother)
(I have no choice but to leave you)
(and head to Wujing.)
(I must seal the spiritual root
in your body.)
(This is the only way)
(to hide your true bloodline.)
(Only by becoming an ordinary person)
(can you)
(avoid the biggest disaster
in your life.)
(Zhilou,)
(don't blame me.)
(Please stay safe.)
Where's Yue?
She knows your feelings for her,
and that you would stop her.
This is her portrait.
(Dark Dhuta, Wujing City's Guardian )
The Wujing City Lord
has ordered to bring back the baby
who was born here not too long ago.
Please hand the baby over now.
Please forgive me.
A while ago,
we had an epidemic.
The baby
has died.
Died?
The baby had high fever for several days
and skin sores oozing pus.
Even their organs were rotting.
Their entire body was rotten.
Even their clothes...
We burned all their clothes too.
I was afraid the sickness would spread.
Men.
Sir,
this is all that's left.
My condolences.
Safe travels, sir.
Qingyun,
from this day on,
tell outsiders
that Yue was my mistress.
She ran away
with another man.
This child has no spiritual root,
but she will be my flesh and blood.
She will live a difficult life
and become your disgrace.
She will be scorned
by the entire Feng family,
and she will hate you.
As long as I can protect Yue's child,
this kind of sacrifice
is nothing.
Dear child,
you will face many hardships,
but I
and Qingyun
still hope you grow up healthy.
One day,
you will soar freely.
(Plaque of Feng Qingfeng,
head of Feng Manor)
I've hated him for so many years
yet didn't know anything.
The family doesn't have a lot of power.
We were afraid the person
trying to harm your mother
would find out about you.
So your father had
to hide your identity.
Uncle Qingyun,
I understand
your selfless efforts.
It's been so many years.
Thank you, Uncle Qingyun.
If you hadn't taught me medicine,
I wouldn't be able to grow up safely
in Feng Manor.
Before Lenghou Ye died,
he sent a letter to Wujing City
claiming
that we called off the engagement
to ally with the Dragons.
But now
you've killed Lengou Ye.
I'm afraid
we can't avoid this trouble.
I will explain
what happened to Wujing City.
If there is punishment,
it is what I should bear too.
The crux of the matter
isn't self-justification,
but whether the Wujing City Lord
is willing to let you off.
She must know
that you didn't disrupt the alliance
between the Saintess and the Dragons
for this matter to be resolved.
The arrangement between me
and Chu Moshang was just a deal.
Besides,
our fake wedding
was never completed.
What do you plan on doing now?
Mother said
she'll return
after her business in Wujing,
but she's lost contact
for so many years.
Tell me.
Did something happen to her,
or is she...?
Now that I know the truth,
I cannot just sit by and do nothing.
I must go to Wujing City
and find my mother.
Have you thought this through?
Wujing
holds grave danger.
Compared to dying in a cage,
I rather fall when flying.
At least I got to see the sky.
(Wujing City)
(Li Liluo, Wujing City's Princess)
Hello, Mother.
Very good.
However, you are still missing an outfit
that is fitting for the status
of the Wujing Saintess.
You love me the most, Mother.
Those are merely superficial gestures
for the sanctuary.
What's important is
the inspection ritual in a few days.
I am the Wujing City Lord.
I cannot show any undue favor
toward you.
But...
I will give you the best things
in this world.
I know you want the best for me,
but I heard
a woman
from the Feng family
married a person impersonating
the Dragon Prince.
They want to ruin my plan.
This is the exact expression.
You must make
the world's most noble man,
the future Dragon King,
to pity you.
Remember.
Your target is to become
the most supreme woman
in this world,
the Dragon Queen.
Only in this way
can we both
truly achieve eternal life.
Greetings, my lord.
Investigate the Feng Manor situation
as quickly as possible.
I will not let anyone
ruin my daughter's plans.
As you command.
Miss Zhilou,
I don't have much to give you.
You can drink this Huodiao wine
on the road.
Miss Zhilou,
thank you so much for your help.
I prepared some everyday clothing.
I hope you don't mind
the simple quality.
Miss Zhilou,
the road is long,
and dangers abound.
Although you possess great skills,
there is always someone greater
out there.
You must be careful.
Yes, be careful.
Thank you
for the kind words.
Everyone,
I will do my utmost
for the trip to Wujing.
I also hope that you all
will take good care of yourselves
and Feng Manor.
Don't worry.
Zhilou!
Zhilou.
Uncle Qingyun.
What are you doing?
Your journey to Wujing City
will bring you
through the Serpent Forest.
That place is full of dangers.
Let me come with you.
I can't let you go alone.
Young Master,
only the surface injuries have healed
from the lighting wound you suffered.
The internal injury
requires you to use your dragon pearl
to nurture it.
You can't use large amounts of energy.
Young Master, the three-day deadline
given by His Majesty is up.
We should set off for Wujing.
We must take the sigil back.
We don't have much time left.
What do you mean, Young Master?
Has Feng Zhilou
left the Feng Manor?
Yes, she has.
She will pass by the Serpent Forest
on her way to Wujing City.
Wujing City received the news
you and Lenghou Ye sent.
I'm afraid you're too late.
Lenghou Ye was killed by Feng Zhilou.
He died
because of his incompetence.
I'm leaving the remaining matter
to you.
Remember.
You can only report to me alive.
If Feng Zhilou doesn't die,
then you...
must die.
This is the Serpents' territory.
Don't let this seemingly
normal forest fool you.
It's filled with poisonous plants.
You must be careful.
We can't see the sky here
and must rely on the leaves'
growth direction to get our bearings.
If we don't have a local guide,
we'll get lost easily.
I stumbled into this place
while gathering herbs years ago
and only got out with someone's help.
Careful, Uncle Qingyun.
Jia Yu?
Jia Yu,
you finally dropped the act.
All these years, it must've been exhausting
for you to put up an act in the Feng Manor.
Feng Zhilou,
when did you find me out?
When you tried to ruin my reputation.
Your pulse
wasn't one of a fool.
Let go.
You came
to stop us from going to Wujing City.
Why is that?
Who exactly are you?
That doesn't matter.
What matters is
Wujing City wants you dead!
Careful, Zhilou!
I have nine spiritual roots now.
Your meager skill
can't stop me.
Wujing has taken notice of you now.
Zhilou,
when you reach Wujing,
you must not
easily reveal anything
about your mother.
Uncle Qingyun.
Uncle Qingyun, where did you go?
Uncle Qingyun!
♪Like petals fall, gone with the clouds♪
♪Like stars fade fast in open skies♪
♪Like snowflakes melting softly
in the evening haze♪
♪Like your fleeting glance
that gave me one brief dream's grace♪
♪Like fireflies flicker
through wild grass, fleeting light♪
♪Like evening breeze
that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪Like fleeting thoughts
that surge and then unwind♪
♪Chance meetings fade,
just empty rooms left behind♪
♪You brought a wave
that stirred a wild, restless sea♪
♪Light as a feather,
yet it sank an island deep in me♪
♪In that one moment,
life's grip I couldn't break or sway♪
♪Leaving me lost in memories,
small and fading away♪